const STORE = [
    {
      question: "What is the surname given to bastards born in Dorne?",
      answers: [
        "Stone",
        "Rivers",
        "Waters",
        "Sand"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Sand",
    },
    {
      question: "'The Mountain' is the nickname for which character?",
      answers: [
        "Gerold Clegane",
        "Oberyn Martel",
        "Gregor Clegane",
        "Sandor Clegane"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Gregor Clegane",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is Lord Commander of the Kingsguard at the beginning of Game of Thrones?",
      answers: [
        "Ser Jaime Lannister",
        "Ser Loras Tyrell",
        "Ser Barristan Selmy",
        "Ser Jeor Mormont"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Ser Barristan Selmy",
    },
    {
      question: "Who was Margaery Tyrell's first husband?",
      answers: [
        "Tommen Baratheon",
        "Stannis Baratheon",
        "Joffrey Baratheon",
        "Renly Baratheon"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Renly Baratheon",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is known as 'The-King-Beyond-the-Wall'?",
      answers: [
        "The Night King",
        "Tormund Giantsbane",
        "Mance Rayder",
        "Stannis Baratheon"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Mance Rayder",
    },
    {
      question: "How many times has Sansa Stark been married?",
      answers: [
        "None",
        "Three times",
        "Twice",
        "Once"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Twice",
    },
    {
      question: "Who delivered the fatal blow to the King-in-the North, Robb Stark?",
      answers: [
        "Walder Frey",
        "Roose Bolton",
        "Ramsay Bolton",
        "Alliser Thorne"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Roose Bolton",
    },
    {
      question: "Grey Worm and Missandei became allies of Daenerys Targaryen after she liberated the slaves of which city?",
      answers: [
        "Yunkai",
        "Meereen",
        "Astapor",
        "Qarth"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Astapor",
    },
    {
      question: "The wildling Gilly has a son, who is the father?",
      answers: [
        "Tormund Giantsbane",
        "Jeor Marmont",
        "Craster",
        "Samwell Tarly"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Craster",
    },
    {
      question: "In which city does Arya Stark train to become a Faceless Man?",
      answers: [
        "Astapor",
        "Braavos",
        "Meereen",
        "Pentos"
        ],
      correctAnswer: "Braavos",
    },
    
  ]